BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
  - Code no.8665: Heavy Construction Section Labor Relations Division of Alabama Branch of Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 312, 1961-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8665: Heavy Construction Section Labor Relations Division of Alabama Branch of Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Jefferson County Alabama and Vicinity Carpenters District C, 1961-1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8665: Heavy Construction Section Labor Relations Division of Alabama Branch of Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers Union of America, 1961-1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8665: Heavy Construction Section Labor Relations Division of Alabama Branch of Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 612, 1961-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Code no.8746: Allied Construction Employers Association, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 139, 1966- 1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Code no.8852: Minneapolis Association of Plumbing Contractors, Inc. and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada Local 15, United Association Plumbers, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Code no.8914: Illinois Regional Insulation Contractors Association, Inc. and International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Local 17, 1965-1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Code no.8409: Associated General Contractors and Phoenix Building and Construction Trades Council, 1959-1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8442: Construction Industry Employers Association and International Association of Bridge, Structural, and Ornamental Ironworkers Local 6, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8444: Construction Industry Employers Association and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America -Carpenters' District Council of Buffalo, New York and Vicinity, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8533: National Electrical Contractors Association, Inc. St. Louis Chapter and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1, 1959-1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Code no.591198: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc., Wisconsin Chapter and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 139, 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Code no.8634: Building Trades Employers' Association and International Hod Carriers Building and Common Laborers' Union, Local 310, 1961- 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8652: Hudson Valley Construction Employers Association and Tri-County Construction Associates and Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters, 1961-1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8657: Great Lakes Fabricators and Erectors Association of Michigan and International Union of Operating Engineers Locals 324 and 324A, 1960-1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8677: Metropolitan Detroit Plumbing and Mechanical Contractors Association, Inc. and Journeymen Pipefitters Local 636, 1970- 1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Code no.8677: Metropolitan Detroit Plumbing-Heating-Cooling Contractors Association and Mechanical Contractors Association of Detroit, Inc. and Journeymen Pipefitters Local 636, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Code no.8677: Metropolitan Detroit Plumbing Contractors Association and Mechanical Contractors' Association of Detroit, Inc. and Journeymen Pipefitters Local 636, 1963-1969 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Code no.8721: Northern Ohio Mason Contractors Association, Inc. and Bricklayers Local Union 5 of Cleveland, Ohio of B.M. & P.I.U., 1964-1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Code no.591168: Sheet Metal Employers' Association and Sheet Metal Workers' International Association Local 65, 1966-1973 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Code no.591158: Baton Rouge Chapter, Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 406, 406A, and 406B, 1967-1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Code no.580169: Associated General Contractors of New Jersey and Independent Contractors and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 676, 1966-1975 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Code no.8743: Florida West Coast Chapter of the Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and Gulf Coast District Council of Carpenters, 1966-1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Code no.8797: General Contractors Association of Akron, Akron Chapter of the Associated General Contractors of America and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Summit, Medina, and Portage Counties District Council of Carpenters, 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Code no.8812: Contractors Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and the Pennsylvania Excavating Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 312, 384, Local 470, 1963-1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Code no.8824: Mechanical Contractors Association of Central Ohio, Inc. and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada, Local 189, 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Code no.8844: Foundation and Marine Contractors Association of New England, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 4, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Code no.8847: Master Builders' Association of Western Pennsylvania, Inc. and Operative Plasterers' and Cement Masons' International Association Local 526, Cement Masons' Union, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Code no.8851: Building Trades Employers' Association of Western Massachusetts, Inc. and Laborers' International Union of North America - Massachusetts Laborers' District Council in behalf of Construction and General Laborers' Local 596, Holyoke, and Cons, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Code no.8865: Northeastern Florida Chapter of the Associated General Contractors of America and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 673, 673A, 673B, and 673C, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Code no.8875: General Contracting Business and Carpenters District Council of Jacksonville and Vicinity, 1968-1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Code no.8881: Florida West Coast Chapter of the Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and North and Central Florida Laborers District Council Locals 512, 1207, and 1240, 1966-1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Code no.8925: General Contracting Business and Laborer's International Union of North America Local 301, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Code no.8931: Contractors of Grand Forks, North Dakota and Laborers International Union of North America Local 580, Laborers District Council of Minnesota and North Dakota, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Code no.8932: Construction Contractors Council and Cement Masons Local 891 of Washington D.C. and Vicinity, 1966-1975 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Code no.8494: Constructors Association of Western Pennsylvania and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1959- 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8494: Constructors Association of Western Pennsylvania and International Union of Operating Engineers, 1959-1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8494: Constructors Association of Western Pennsylvania and Laborers' District Council of Western Pennsylvania, 1959- 1971 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Code no.8494: Constructors Association of Western Pennsylvania and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Joint Council No. 40, 1959-1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Code no.8517: Builders' Association of Kansas City, Missouri and Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, Painters' District Council No. 3, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Code no.8519: Chicago Council of the Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Painters' District Council No. 14, 1967-1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Code no.8553: Executive Council of the California Conference of Mason Contractor Associations, Inc. and Southern California District Council of Laborers, Locals 220, 300, 439, 507, 652, 802, 806, 1082, and 585, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Code no.8616: San Antonio Chapter, Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 14, 1965-1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Code no.8622: Builders Association of Kansas City and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council of Kansas City and Vicinity, 1966-1973 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Code no.8626: No Employer and Carpenters' District Council of Milwaukee County and Vicinity, 1968-1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Code no.8627: No Employer and Dock Builders, Shorers, and Pile Drivers Local 1456, 1960-1972 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Code no.8669: Associated Plumbing, Heating, and Piping Contractors of New Mexico, Inc. and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada Local 412, 1963-1974 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Code no.8691: Mechanical Contractors District of Columbia Association, Inc. and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the United States and Canada Local 602, 1963-1972 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Code no.8692: West Virginia Heavy and Highway Contractors Bargaining Committee and United Mine Workers of America District 50, 1963- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Code no.8782: Hudson Valley Construction Employers Association and Laborers' International Union of North America Local 17, 1967- 1973 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Code no.8786: General Contractors Association of Louisville, Inc.; Mason Contractors Association of Louisville, Inc.; Cooperative Plasterers Association of Louisville and Laborers' International Union of North America Local 576, 1965-1973 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Code no.8796: Sheet Metal Contractors of the District of Columbia and Vicinity and Sheet Metal Workers Local 102, 1963-1972 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Code no.8806: Rocky Mountain Chapter National Electrical Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 68, 1965-1975 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Code no.8809: Contractors' Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 542, 542A, and 542B, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Code no.8811: Contractors' Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Carpenters' Joint Council of Eastern Pennsylvania, 1964-1973 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Code no.8846: Connecticut Labor Relations Division of the New England Road Builders Association, Inc. and Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers' International Union of America, Connecticut State Conference, 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Code no.8857: Association of Steel Erectors and Heavy Equipment Operators, Inc. and Iron Workers Local 387, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Code no.8868: No Employer and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council of New York City and Vicinity, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Code no.8872: Several Employers and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council of New York City and Vicinity, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Code no.8901: Plumbing, Heating, and Air Conditioning Contractor Members of the Lehigh Valley Construction Council and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada, Local 670, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Code no.8903: Associated General Contractors, Arkansas Chapter and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 690, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Code no.8926: General Contractors Association of Lehigh Valley, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Lehigh Valley District Council, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Code no.8438: Construction Contractors Council and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 77, 1951-1975 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Code no.8461: Southwestern Michigan Contractors Association and State of Michigan Laborers' District Council, 1959-1974 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Code no.8462: Labor Relations Division of the Ohio Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - Ohio Conference of Teamsters, 1959-1975 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Code no.8488: Keystone Building Contractors Association and Laborers' District Council of Western Pennsylvania, Locals 910, 824, 419, 1959- 1973 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Code no.8492: Building Trades Employers Association and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 4, Hoisting and Portable Engineers, 1961-1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Code no.8526: Minneapolis Chapter, Inc., Minnesota Council, Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, Local 386, 1960-1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Code no.590288: Associated Tile Contractors of Southern California and Tile Layers Union No. 18 of California, B.M.P.I.U. of A., 1969- 1972 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Code no.8554: Executive Council of the California Conference of Mason Contractor Associations, Inc. and Bricklayers' and Stonemasons' Union Locals 2, 13, 15, 22, 26, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Code no.8580: Associated Steel Erectors of Chicago and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 1, 1969-1973 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Code no.8594: Master Builders' Association of Western Pennsylvania, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 66, 1970- 1973 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Code no.8621: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and Carpenters District Council of Jacksonville and Vicinity, 1973- 1976 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Code no.560832: Memphis Chapter, Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and Laborers' International Union of North America, Local 1441, 1966-1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Code no.8646: Building Trades Employers Association and Laborers International Union of North America, Local 435, 1962-1974 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Code no.8656: Michigan Chapter, Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 324, 324A, 324B, 324C, 1960-1970 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Code no.591294: Glass Management Association and Glaziers and Glass Workers Locals 169, 718, 1621, 1962-1973 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8404: Building Trades Employers' Association of Boston and International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers Union of America Locals 22, 88, 133, 138, 151, 223, 243, 290, 560, 609, 721, Eastern Massachusetts Laborers' District Council, 1958-1974 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Series V: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
  - Code no.255: Campbell Soup Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local P-80-A, 1970- 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Code no.591263: Associated Brewers Inc. and United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America, Brewery Workers Joint Local Executive Board of Baltimore, Maryland, representing Local Unions 10 and 177, 1961-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Code no.332: Campbell Soup Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 146, Cannery and Allied Workers Union, 1964-1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Code no.813: Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (Dress Branch) and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; St. Louis Joint Board; Northern Missouri, Minnesota, and Iowa District Council; and Southern Illinois District Council, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Code no.249: No Employer and Seafarers International Union of North America, United Cannery and Industrial Workers of the Pacific, 1968- 1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Code no.277: Federation of New England Bakery Employers and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, New England Bakery Drivers Council, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Code no.378: Gwaltney Inc. and Employees Beneficial Association No.2, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Code no.850: Infant and Juvenile Manufacturers Association, Inc. and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Local 169, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Washable Clothing, Sportswear, and Novelty Workers, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Code no.591061: Bedding Industry and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, Furniture Union Local 500, 1962-1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Code no.264: Stokely-Van Camp, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Locals 56, 563, 662, 695, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Code no.590493: No Employer and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, Local 338, 1969-1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Code no.560775: Levers Lace Manufacturers of America, Inc. and Amalgamated Lace Operatives of America, Lever Section, 1966- 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Code no.270: Kellogg Co. and American Federation of Grain Millers Local 252, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Code no.319: Schenley Distillers, Inc. and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America, Local 6, 1969- 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Code no.620: Munsingwear, Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, Locals 66, 1254, 1256, 1259, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Code no.830: Needle Trades Employers Association and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Locals 178, 324, 232, 361, 1970- 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Code no.853: Associated Fur Manufacturers, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Furriers Joint Council of New York, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Code no.1107: No Employer and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, Upholsterers, Decorators, and Allied Crafts Union, Local 44, 1966-1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Series VI: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Code no.4418: GAF Corporation and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 306, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Code no.4611: Armstrong Cork Company, Lancaster Floor Plant and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, Local 285, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Code no.4613: New York Mounters Association, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local 107, 1962- 1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Code no.6325: Northern Illinois Ready Mix and Materials Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 786, 782, 801, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Code no.591188: American Greetings Corp. and Independent Greeting Card Workers Union, 1962-1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Code no.1625: FMC Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, Local 713, CLC, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Code no.1643: Lederle Laboratories Division, American Cyanamid Company and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 143, 1971- 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1690: E.I. De Pont De Nemours and Company and Old Hickory Employees' Council, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Code no.590261: Huron Cement, Division of National Gypsum Company and United Stone and Allied Products, Local 135, 1969- 1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2336: Johns-Manville Products Corporation and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 60, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Code no.1128: MPI Industries, Division of Desoto, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 3031, 1970- 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Code no.1205: Champion Papers Division of U.S. Plywood-Champion Papers Inc. and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Code no.1423: Printers League Section, Printing Industries and New York Paper Cutters' and Bookbinders' Union No. 119, 1971- 1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1641: Union Carbide Corp., Chemicals and Plastics Operations Division and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-891, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Code no.1003: Potlatch Forests, Inc., Southern Division, Wood Products Group and International Woodworkers of America, Local 5-484, 1970- 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Code no.590711: Graphic Arts Association of Michigan, Inc., Pressmen Union Employers' Section and Detroit Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union No. 2, 1963-1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Code no.591369: E.I. De Pont De Nemours and Company and Neoprene Craftsmen Union, 1961-1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Code no.590304: Hercules Inc. and International Chemical Workers Union Local 271, 1968-1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Code no.1645: E.R. Squibb and Sons, Inc., Production and Maintenance and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-438, 1967-1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1272: U.S. Plywood-Champion Papers Inc. and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local 507, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Code no.1288: Crown Zellerbach Corporation and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, Locals 68 and 166, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Code no.1447: National Blank Book Company, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 48, 1968-1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Code no.1456: Printers League Section, Printing Industries and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders Local 43, Bindery Women's Union, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Code no.1632: E.I. De Pont De Nemours and Company and Martinsville Nylon Employees' Council Corporation, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Code no.1653: Sherwin-Williams Co. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 7-268, 1961-1972 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Code no.2332: Carborundum Co. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-12058, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.4148: Harley-Davidson Motor Co. Inc. and Allied Industrial Workers, Local 209, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Code no.4152: Detroit Gasket & Manufacturing Company and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1958-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Code no.4154: The South Bend Division of Kaiser Jeep Corporation and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local No. 5 (Kaiser Jeep Unit), 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Code no.4179: Bethlehem Steel Corporation (Shipbuilding Department) and Beaumont Metal Trades Council AFL-CIO, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Code no.4179: Bethlehem Steel Corporation (Shipbuilding Department) and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry of the United States and Canada, Local 195, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Code no.4179: Bethlehem Steel Corporation (Shipbuilding Department) and International Association of Machinists, Local 395, 1966- 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Code no.4183: Howmet Corporation Misco Division and Reactive Metal Products Division and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1243, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Code no.4400: ARMA Division of American Bosch ARMA Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 460, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Code no.4401: ARMA Division of American Bosch ARMA Corporation and Engineers Association of ARMA, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)